Hello, this is Vue Roadmap, a mobile app designed to guide you through a 14-day Vue 3 self-study sprint.
After downloading the release APK, install the app on your Android phone and open it.
When the app opens, start in the Today tab. Tap Start Sprint Today. This becomes your main learning screen for the whole sprint.
Each day shows your objective, what you need to know, what to study, what to research, what to build, and how to know you are on track.
If you want to see the full journey, open the Roadmap tab. It contains all 14 days with detailed guidance.
Use Checklist to mark your daily routine, checkpoint progress, and completed days.
If you forget how the app works, open the Guide tab. It explains what each screen does and how to move through the sprint.
Use Tracker to record your confidence for each day and save short notes about what felt easy or difficult.
As you move through the sprint, the app also points you toward the mini project you are building.
The best way to use Vue Roadmap is simple: open Today, follow the guidance, build the feature, check your progress, and write a short note before you stop.